Faculty of Interdisciplinary Studies fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Curriculum and instruction, 1971 - 1985; F-23-5; 2.08 m of textual records
  - Undergraduate Curriculum Committee, 1972 - 1985; F-23-5-1; 1.03 m of textual records
    - UGCC - Paper 81-30: Canadian Studies Curriculum Changes - Joint Major Requirements, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-120 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-32: Management and Systems Science - Curricular Changes, 81-32, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-121 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-33a: New Course Proposal - General Studies 352, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-123 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-33: Certificate Program in Interdisciplinary Study of the family, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-124 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-35: Change in University Regulations 1) Add/Drop 2) Duplicate Courses, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-125 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 81-36: New Course Proposal - Economics 455-3, Consider for Overlap, 1981; F-23-5-1-0-126 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 82-02: Curriculum Changes - Kinesiology, 1982; F-23-5-1-0-127 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 82-03: New Course Proposal - Centre for the Arts, Fine and Performing Arts 105-3, 1982; F-23-5-1-0-128 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 82-04-: BC Studies Certificate Course Changes Concerning Canadian Studies, 1982; F-23-5-1-0-129 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 82-05: Kinesiology New Course Proposal - Kinesiology 415-3, 1982; F-23-5-1-0-130 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 82-06: Centre for the Arts New Course Proposal - Selected Topics and Directed Studies, 1982; F-23-5-1-0-131 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 82-07: Computing Science Enrollment Priority, 1982; F-23-5-1-0-132 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 82-08: Criminology Curriculum Changes, 1982; F-23-5-1-0-133 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 82-09: Management and Systems Science Curriculum Changes, 1982; F-23-5-1-0-134 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 82-10: Kinesiology New Programs, 1982; F-23-5-1-0-135 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 82-11: Senior Citizens Certificate Program/Proposed Calendar Changes, 1982; F-23-5-1-0-136 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 82-12: Women's Studies 100 Change in Vector/Credit Hours, 1982; F-23-5-1-0-137 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 82-13: New Course Proposal - General Studies 210-3, 1982; F-23-5-1-0-138 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 82-14: New Course Proposal - Women's Studies 204, 1982; F-23-5-1-0-139 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 82-16: Computer Literacy Report, 1982; F-23-5-1-0-140 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 82-17: Requirements for a Major in Communications, 1982; F-23-5-1-0-141 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 82-18: Award of B.Sc. (Kinesiology) to Students Transferring to Professional School, 1982; F-23-5-1-0-142 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 82-19: Joint Honours Degree Program in Mathematics and Computing, 1982; F-23-5-1-0-143 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 82-20: Centre for the Arts Curriculum Changes, 1982; F-23-5-1-0-144 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 82-21: Management Systems Science, 1982; F-23-5-1-0-145 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 82-22: SUAB-FISC Faculty Members to Senate Undergraduate Admissions Board, 1982; F-23-5-1-0-146 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 82-23: Calendar Changes - Department of Communications, 1982; F-23-5-1-0-147 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 82-24: Additions of Courses to the Canadian Content List, 1982; F-23-5-1-0-148 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 82-25: Summary of Proposed Calendar Changes, 1982; F-23-5-1-0-149 (Archival box - standard 23-24)
    - UGCC - Paper 82-26: Proposed Revisions to the B.G.S. Regulations, 1982; F-23-5-1-0-150 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 82-27: Kinesiology Curriculum Changes, 1982; F-23-5-1-0-151 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 82-28: Curriculum Change - Africa/Middle East, 1982; F-23-5-1-0-152 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 82-29: Calendar Changes - Women's Studies, 1982; F-23-5-1-0-153 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 82-30: Calendar Changes - Computing, 1982; F-23-5-1-0-154 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 82-31: Calendar Changes - Communications, 1982; F-23-5-1-0-155 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 82-32: Continuance, Withdrawal and Readmission from SUAB, 1982; F-23-5-1-0-156 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 83-01: New Honours Program - Kinesiology, 1983; F-23-5-1-0-157 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 83-02: Change of General Studies 402-5 and Deletion of General Studies 403-5, 1983; F-23-5-1-0-158 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 83-02a: Acceptability of C- as a Satisfactory Grade, 1983; F-23-5-1-0-159 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 83-03: Quorum, 1983; F-23-5-1-0-160 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 83-04 - Summary of Proposed Calendar Change - Centre for the Arts, 1983; F-23-5-1-0-161 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 83-05: Extended Studies Diploma - Kinesiology, 1983; F-23-5-1-0-162 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 83-06: New Course Proposal - Kinesiology, 1983; F-23-5-1-0-163 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 83-07: New Course Proposal - Kinesiology 325-3, 1983; F-23-5-1-0-164 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 83-08: New Course Proposal - Communications 439-4, 1983; F-23-5-1-0-165 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 83-09: Certificate of Health and Fitness Optional Courses - Kinesiology Department, 1983; F-23-5-1-0-166 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 83-10: SFU Admission Requirements/DISC, 1983; F-23-5-1-0-167 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 83-11: Admission to Certificate Program, 1983; F-23-5-1-0-168 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 83-13: Proposed Estonian Studies, 1983; F-23-5-1-0-169 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 83-14: (Definition of C Minus), 1983; F-23-5-1-0-170 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 83-15: Change of Vector - Kinesiology 320, 1983; F-23-5-1-0-171 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 83-16: Faculty Curriculum Committee - Centre for the Arts, 1983; F-23-5-1-0-172 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 83-17: English Language Proficiency, 1983; F-23-5-1-0-173 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 83-18: Proposed Change - Final Exam Scheduling, 1983; F-23-5-1-0-174 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 83-19: Curriculum Change - Centre for Canadian Studies, 1983; F-23-5-1-0-175 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 83-20: New Course Proposal - Women's Studies 205-3, 1983; F-23-5-1-0-176 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 83-21: Change of Credit Hours - Kinesiology Courses, 1983; F-23-5-1-0-177 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 83-22 and 22a: New Course Proposal - Gerontology, 1983; F-23-5-1-0-178 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 83-23: Calendar Changes - Department of Computing Science, 1983; F-23-5-1-0-179 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 83-23a: New Course Proposals - Computing Science, Mathematics, Biology, 1984; F-23-5-1-0-180 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 83-24: Curriculum Changes - Department of Criminology, 1984; F-23-5-1-0-181 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 83-25: New Course Proposal - Gerontology 401-3, 1984; F-23-5-1-0-182 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 83-26: Communications Undergraduate Calendar Change, 1984; F-23-5-1-0-183 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 83-27: Centre for the Arts Curriculum, 1983; F-23-5-1-0-184 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 83-28: New Course Proposal - Gerontology 401-3, 1983; F-23-5-1-0-185 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 83-29: New Course Proposal - Gerontology 410-3, 1983; F-23-5-1-0-186 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 83-30: Calendar Change - Women's Studies, 1983; F-23-5-1-0-187 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 84-01: New Communications Course Proposals [file missing], 1984; F-23-5-1-0-188
    - UGCC - Paper 84-02: Enrollment Limitations - Interdisciplinary Studies, 1984; F-23-5-1-0-189 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 84-03: Draft Motion on Minimum Grade Point Average, 1984; F-23-5-1-0-190 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 84-06: Deletion of Geography 467-5 for the Latin American Studies/Geography Joint Major Requirements, 1984; F-23-5-1-0-191 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 84-07: Deletion of Non-Credit Activities in the Certificate of Health and Fitness, 1984; F-23-5-1-0-192 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 84-08: Scheduling of Classes, 1984; F-23-5-1-0-193 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 84-09: Enrollment Priority, 1984; F-23-5-1-0-194 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 84-10: FISC, 1984; F-23-5-1-0-195 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 84-11: FISC, 1984; F-23-5-1-0-196 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 84-12: FISC, 1984; F-23-5-1-0-197 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 84-13: Assessment of Content of Multiple University Degrees (M.U.D.), 1984; F-23-5-1-0-198 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 84-14: Proposal for Athletics Courses in Service to the Secondary Physical Education, 1984; F-23-5-1-0-199 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 84-15: Elections - Senate Undergraduate Admission Board, 1984; F-23-5-1-0-200 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 84-16: Grade Point Average - Gerontology, 1984; F-23-5-1-0-201 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 84-17: Enrollment Restriction, 1984; F-23-5-1-0-202 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 84-18: Addition to upper Division Kinesiology Electives, 1984; F-23-5-1-0-203 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 84-19: Prerequisite for Kinesiology 303-3 - Department of Kinesiology, 1984; F-23-5-1-0-204 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 84-20: Curriculum Changes - Department of Computing Science, 1984; F-23-5-1-0-205 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 84-21: Prerequisite Changes - Centre for the Arts, 1984; F-23-5-1-0-206 (Archival box - standard 23-25)
    - UGCC - Paper 84-22: Proposed Calendar Changes for Technical Theatre Courses: Centre for the Arts, 1984; F-23-5-1-0-207 (Archival box - standard 23-26)
    - UGCC - Paper 84-23: Proposed Curriculum Changes - Computing Science, 1984; F-23-5-1-0-208 (Archival box - standard 23-26)
    - UGCC - Paper 84-24: Title Change for Women's Studies 220-3, 1984; F-23-5-1-0-209 (Archival box - standard 23-26)
    - UGCC - Paper 84-25: Change in Prerequisite - Women's Studies 401-5, 1984; F-23-5-1-0-210 (Archival box - standard 23-26)
    - UGCC - Paper 84-26: Gerontology Restriction on Applicability of Psychology 44-5 to DGT, 1984; F-23-5-1-0-211 (Archival box - standard 23-26)
    - UGCC - Paper 84-27: Change in Prerequisite for Gerontology 410-3: Gerontology, 1984; F-23-5-1-0-212 (Archival box - standard 23-26)
    - UGCC - Correspondence, 1972 - 1981; F-23-5-1-0-213 (Archival box - standard 23-26)
    - UGCC - Correspondence, 1976 - 1983; F-23-5-1-0-214 (Archival box - standard 23-26)
    - UGCC - Courses approved by Senate 1/2, 1972 - 1973; F-23-5-1-0-215 (Archival box - standard 23-26)
    - UGCC - Courses approved by Senate 2/2, 1972 - 1973; F-23-5-1-0-216 (Archival box - standard 23-26)
    - UGCC - Courses not approved, 1973 - 1976; F-23-5-1-0-217 (Archival box - standard 23-26)
  - Graduate Studies Committee, 1973 - 1984; F-23-5-2; 5 cm of textual records
    Series consists of records relating to the development and delivery of courses to graduate students. GRIDS was composed of one faculty member from each department or program offering a graduate degree, the Associate Dean, and two students. Series includes agendas, minutes, correspondence, working papers and other documents.
    - GSC - Agenda/Minutes, 1979 - 1983; F-23-5-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 23-26)
    - GSC - Papers, 1973 - 1978; F-23-5-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 23-26)
    - GSC - Papers, 1979 - 1981; F-23-5-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 23-26)
    - GSC - Papers, 1982 - 1984; F-23-5-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 23-26)
    - GSC - Papers, 1983; F-23-5-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 23-27)
  - Program proposals, 1971 - 1984; F-23-5-3; 71 cm of textual records
    Series consists of records relating to the development of new courses and programs in the Faculty of Interdisciplinary Studies and includes both successful and unsuccessful proposals. Series includes proposals, correspondence, reports, working papers, and other documents.
    - General, 1978 - 1980; F-23-5-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 23-27)
    - General, 1982 - 1983; F-23-5-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 23-27)
    - Arts program, 1975 - 1976; F-23-5-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 23-27)
    - Bachelor of General Studies (Education), 1976; F-23-5-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 23-27)
    - Biostatistics, 1978; F-23-5-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 23-27)
    - Canadian and Women's Studies, 1980 - 1982; F-23-5-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 23-27)
    - Coaching Certificate, 1974 - 1979; F-23-5-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 23-27)
    - Coaching Specialist Minor proposal, 1976; F-23-5-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 23-27)
    - Communication Studies, 1971 - 1972; F-23-5-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 23-27)
    - Communication Studies 1/2, 1972; F-23-5-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 23-27)
    - Communication Studies 2/2, 1972; F-23-5-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 23-27)
    - Communication Studies Certificate, 1977; F-23-5-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 23-27)
    - Proposed program for a Department of Communication Studies 1/2, 1972; F-23-5-3-0-13 (Archival box - standard 23-27)
    - Proposed program for a Department of Communication Studies 2/2, 1972; F-23-5-3-0-14 (Archival box - standard 23-28)
    - Communications Studies - Graduate proposal, 1972; F-23-5-3-0-15 (Archival box - standard 23-28)
    - Communication Studies - Ph.D. proposal, 1980 - 1981; F-23-5-3-0-16 (Archival box - standard 23-28)
    - Communications Studies - Ph.D. proposal, 1983; F-23-5-3-0-17 (Archival box - standard 23-28)
    - Communications and Computer research laboratory, 1982; F-23-5-3-0-18 (Archival box - standard 23-28)
    - Computer Engineering / Computer Physics, 1976; F-23-5-3-0-19 (Archival box - standard 23-28)
    - Criminology, 1971 - 1973; F-23-5-3-0-20 (Archival box - standard 23-28)
    - Criminology - undergraduate program, 1974; F-23-5-3-0-21 (Archival box - standard 23-28)
    - Criminology - graduate program, 1975; F-23-5-3-0-22 (Archival box - standard 23-28)
    - Criminology - off-campus program, 1974; F-23-5-3-0-23 (Archival box - standard 23-28)
    - Criminology - graduate program, 1982; F-23-5-3-0-24 (Archival box - standard 23-29)
    - Criminology - graduate degree revision proposal, 1983 - 1984; F-23-5-3-0-25 (Archival box - standard 23-29)
    - Engineering - Faculty proposal, 1980; F-23-5-3-0-26 (Archival box - standard 23-29)
    - Environment Studies, 1971 - 1973; F-23-5-3-0-27 (Archival box - standard 23-29)
    - Ethnic Studies, 1983 - 1984; F-23-5-3-0-28 (Archival box - standard 23-29)
    - Fine Arts, 1976; F-23-5-3-0-29 (Archival box - standard 23-29)
    - Forensic Science, 1977; F-23-5-3-0-30 (Archival box - standard 23-29)
    - Forestry and Resource Management, 1981; F-23-5-3-0-31 (Archival box - standard 23-29)
    - French Western Canada Studies, 1977; F-23-5-3-0-32 (Archival box - standard 23-29)
    - Gerontology 1/2, 1981; F-23-5-3-0-33 (Archival box - standard 23-29)
    - Gerontology 2/2, 1981; F-23-5-3-0-34 (Archival box - standard 23-29)
    - Gerontology, 1981 - 1982; F-23-5-3-0-35 (Archival box - standard 23-29)
    - History and Philosophy of Science, 1972 - 1973; F-23-5-3-0-36 (Archival box - standard 23-30)
    - Hospital Administration, 1974 - 1975; F-23-5-3-0-37 (Archival box - standard 23-30)
    - Human Services Diploma, 1980 - 1981; F-23-5-3-0-38 (Archival box - standard 23-30)
    - Indian Studies, 1972; F-23-5-3-0-39 (Archival box - standard 23-30)
    - Interactive Media, 1972; F-23-5-3-0-40 (Archival box - standard 23-30)
    - Journalism, 1980; F-23-5-3-0-41 (Archival box - standard 23-30)
    - International Development Institute, 1982 - 1984; F-23-5-3-0-42 (Archival box - standard 23-30)
    - Labour Studies, 1975 - 1976; F-23-5-3-0-43 (Archival box - standard 23-30)
    - Legal Studies, 1978; F-23-5-3-0-45 (Archival box - standard 23-30)
    - Liberal Studies, 1975; F-23-5-3-0-46 (Archival box - standard 23-30)
    - Mathematics and Computing Science Honors program, 1983; F-23-5-3-0-47 (Archival box - standard 23-30)
    - Museology, 1979; F-23-5-3-0-48 (Archival box - standard 23-30)
    - Native Indians, 1975; F-23-5-3-0-49 (Archival box - standard 23-30)
    - Occupational Health Science, 1977 - 1979; F-23-5-3-0-50 (Archival box - standard 23-30)
    - Occupational Health Science, 1979 - 1980; F-23-5-3-0-51 (Archival box - standard 23-30)
    - Occupational Health Science 1/3, 1980; F-23-5-3-0-52 (Archival box - standard 23-30)
    - Occupational Health Science 2/3, 1980; F-23-5-3-0-53 (Archival box - standard 23-30)
    - Occupational Health Science 3/3, 1980; F-23-5-3-0-54 (Archival box - standard 23-30)
    - Occupational Health Science 1/2, 1980 - 1981; F-23-5-3-0-55 (Archival box - standard 23-31)
    - Occupational Health Science 2/2, 1980 - 1981; F-23-5-3-0-56 (Archival box - standard 23-31)
    - Occupational Health Science, 1981; F-23-5-3-0-57 (Archival box - standard 23-31)
    - Occupational Health Science, 1981 - 1982; F-23-5-3-0-58 (Archival box - standard 23-31)
    - Prison Education, 1984; F-23-5-3-0-59 (Archival box - standard 23-31)
    - Project Management, 1980; F-23-5-3-0-60 (Archival box - standard 23-31)
    - Recreation, 1976; F-23-5-3-0-61 (Archival box - standard 23-31)
    - Religious Studies, 1979; F-23-5-3-0-62 (Archival box - standard 23-31)
    - Sport BC Fitness and Training Centre, 1980 - 1981; F-23-5-3-0-63 (Archival box - standard 23-31)
    - Sport BC Fitness and Training Centre, 1979 - 1980; F-23-5-3-0-64 (Archival box - standard 23-31)
    - Sports Administration - B.Comm, 1972 - 1973; F-23-5-3-0-65 (Archival box - standard 23-31)
    - Science Studies - Meetings, 1979; F-23-5-3-0-66 (Archival box - standard 23-31)
    - Senior Citizens, 1974; F-23-5-3-0-67 (Archival box - standard 23-31)
    - Survey Science, 1977 - 1978; F-23-5-3-0-68 (Archival box - standard 23-31)
    - Vocational Rehabilitation Counselors, 1981; F-23-5-3-0-69 (Archival box - standard 23-32)
    - Women's Studies - graduate program, 1981; F-23-5-3-0-70 (Archival box - standard 23-32)
    - Women's Studies - MA, 1981 - 1984; F-23-5-3-0-71 (Archival box - standard 23-32)
    - Special Topics Courses, 1977 - 1981; F-23-5-3-0-72 (Archival box - standard 23-32)
    - Correspondence - Universities Council of BC, 1977 - 1984; F-23-5-3-0-73 (Archival box - standard 23-32)
    - Correspondence - Universities Council of BC, 1979 - 1981; F-23-5-3-0-74 (Archival box - standard 23-32)
    - Correspondence - Universities Council of BC, 1982; F-23-5-3-0-75 (Archival box - standard 23-32)
  - General Studies course files, 1971 - 1986; F-23-5-4; 27 cm of textual records
    Series consists of records relating to the delivery of General Studies courses within the Faculty of Interdisciplinary Studies. Series includes course descriptions, administrative forms and correspondence, and sample exams and assignments. Series also includes student proposals for individual studies projects in 400-level courses.
    In November 2003, files previously numbered 1 through 69 were weeded and re-arranged by course number. Files numbers 1 through 69 were then retired. The new files are numbered 70 through 99.
    - FPA 114-6, 250-3, 1976; F-23-5-4-0-70 (Archival box - standard 23-33)
    - GS 075-2, 1971 - 1975; F-23-5-4-0-71 (Archival box - standard 23-33)
    - GS 100-3, 1972 - 1977; F-23-5-4-0-72 (Archival box - standard 23-33)
    - GS 101-3, 1973 - 1974; F-23-5-4-0-73 (Archival box - standard 23-33)
    - GS 102-3, 1974 - 1977; F-23-5-4-0-74 (Archival box - standard 23-33)
    - GS 103-3, 1975 - 1976; F-23-5-4-0-75 (Archival box - standard 23-33)
    - GS 104-3, 1974 - 1978; F-23-5-4-0-76 (Archival box - standard 23-33)
    - GS 106-3, 1976 - 1978; F-23-5-4-0-77 (Archival box - standard 23-33)
    - GS 110-6, 1976; F-23-5-4-0-78 (Archival box - standard 23-33)
    - GS 140-3; 142-3, 1976; F-23-5-4-0-79 (Archival box - standard 23-33)
    - GS 200-3, 1973 - 1976; F-23-5-4-0-80 (Archival box - standard 23-33)
    - GS 201-3, 1976 - 1978; F-23-5-4-0-81 (Archival box - standard 23-33)
    - GS 227-3; 230-3, 1980; F-23-5-4-0-82 (Archival box - standard 23-33)
    - GS 300-5, 1976 - 1978; F-23-5-4-0-83 (Archival box - standard 23-33)
    - GS 301-3; 302-3; 303-3; 350-3; 351-3, 1974 - 1986; F-23-5-4-0-84 (Archival box - standard 23-33)
    - GS 400-5, 1974 - 1976; F-23-5-4-0-85 (Archival box - standard 23-33)
    - GS 400-5, 1977; F-23-5-4-0-86 (Archival box - standard 23-33)
    - GS 400-5, 1978; F-23-5-4-0-87 (Archival box - standard 23-33)
    - GS 400-5, 1979; F-23-5-4-0-88 (Archival box - standard 23-33)
    - GS 400-5, 1980; F-23-5-4-0-89 (Archival box - standard 23-34)
    - GS 400-5, 1981; F-23-5-4-0-90 (Archival box - standard 23-34)
    - GS 400-5, 1981; F-23-5-4-0-91 (Archival box - standard 23-34)
    - GS 402-5; 403-5, 1977 - 1978; F-23-5-4-0-92 (Archival box - standard 23-34)
    - GS 410-3; 411-5, 1979 - 1981; F-23-5-4-0-93 (Archival box - standard 23-34)
    - GS 427-5, 1975 - 1977; F-23-5-4-0-94 (Archival box - standard 23-34)
    - GS 499-15, 1973 - 1975; F-23-5-4-0-95 (Archival box - standard 23-34)
    - GS 499-15, 1976; F-23-5-4-0-96 (Archival box - standard 23-34)
    - GS 499-15, 1977; F-23-5-4-0-97 (Archival box - standard 23-34)
    - GS 499-15, 1978 - 1981; F-23-5-4-0-98 (Archival box - standard 23-34)
    - General Studies courses - correspondence, 1985; F-23-5-4-0-99 (Archival box - standard 23-34)
- Faculty records, 1965 - 1983; F-23-6; 51 cm of textual records
  Series consists of the Faculty personnel files for individual faculty members. Series includes curriculum vitas, letters of appointment, and correspondence about hiring, promotion, and awarding of tenure.
  - Faculty - A, 1981; F-23-6-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 23-35)
  - Faculty - A, 1981 - 1983; F-23-6-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 23-35)
  - Faculty - B, 1978 - 1980; F-23-6-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 23-35)
  - Faculty - B, 1977 - 1981; F-23-6-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 23-35)
  - Faculty - B, 1978 - 1981; F-23-6-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 23-35)
  - Faculty - B, 1967 - 1980; F-23-6-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 23-35)
  - Faculty - C, 1981 - 1982; F-23-6-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 23-35)
  - Faculty - C, 1975 - 1980; F-23-6-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 23-35)
  - Faculty - C, 1982; F-23-6-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 23-35)
  - Faculty - D, 1975 - 1980; F-23-6-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 23-35)
  - Faculty - D, 1982; F-23-6-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 23-35)